<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastian Koehler</title>
    <link>https://pmecon.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sebastian Koehler</description>
    <image>
      <title>Sebastian Koehler</title>
      <url>https://pmecon.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://pmecon.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <atom:link href="https://pmecon.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pmecon.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pmecon.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About I am a Lecturer in Political Economy at the Department of Political Economy at King’s College London and proud father of a lovely daughter. Since March 2022 I am the Academic Convenor of the ECPR Methods School. I am also a member of the editorial board of SN Social Sciences.
My main research interests are in the fields of Political Economy and Political Science. I focus on understanding the role of institutions and their impact on strategic interactions in politics, in particular regarding lobbying, legislative politics, as well as bargaining and political decision-making.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pmecon.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pmecon.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Office hours Tuesday: 15.00-16.00
Thursday: 14.00-15.00
Book here
Contact details Postal address:
King&amp;rsquo;s College London
Department of Political Economy
Bush House North East
30 Aldwych
London WC2B 4BG
United Kingdom
Office:
Virginia Woolf Building
22 Kingsway
London WC2B 6LE
Room 3.37
Email: sebastian.1.koehler@kcl.ac.uk
Office Phone: +44 (0)20 7870 3662
Matrix: @sk3551:matrix.org
XMPP/Jabber: sebkoehle@xmpp.is
View Larger Map
Personal website at King&amp;rsquo;s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pmecon.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pmecon.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>CV You can download my CV here:
Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; / [pdf] View the PDF file here. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pmecon.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pmecon.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Publications Peer Reviewed Stockemer, Daniel/Koehler, Sebastian/Lentz, Tobias. 2018. “Data Access and Transparency: New insights from the political behavior literature.” PS: Political Science and Politics 51 (4): 799–803.
Koehler, Sebastian/König, Thomas. 2015. “Fiscal Governance in the Eurozone: How Effectively Does the Stability and Growth Pact Limit Governmental Debt in the Euro Countries?” Po- litical Science Research and Methods 03(2): 329-352.
Books Koehler, Sebastian. 2019. “Lobbying, Political Uncertainty and Policy Outcomes”. London &amp;amp; New York: Palgrave Macmillan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pmecon.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pmecon.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching King&amp;rsquo;s College London Module Term 7SSPN128 - Climate Change Ecoomics and Policy Term 2, 2023/2024 5SSPP266 - Introduction to climate change Policy Term 1, 2023/2024 5SSPP245 - Statistics for Political Science Term 1, 2023/2024 7SSPN107 - Quantitative Methods for Political Economy Term 1, 2023/2024 4SSPP103 - Comparing Political Systems Term 2, 2022/2023 5SSPP211 - Institutions, Economics, and Change Term 2, 2022/2023 7SSPN128 - Economics and Policy of Climate Change Term 2, 2022/2023 7SSPN107 - Quantitative Methods in Political Economy Term 1, 2022/2023 5SSPP245 - Statistics for Political Science Term 1, 2022/2023 5SSPP245 - Statistics for Political Science Term 2, 2021/2022 5SSPP211 - Institutions, Economics, and Change Term 2, 2021/2022 4SSPP103 - Comparing Political Systems Term 2, 2021/2022 University of Innsbruck Title Semester PS Statistik Spring 2024 VU Methoden Fall 2023 University of Konstanz Title Semester Analyzing Politics: Strategy and Institutions Winter 2021 Causal Inference for Policy Evaluation Summer 2021 Interest Group Politics Summer 2021 The Political Economy of Electoral Accountability Winter 2020 Legislative Politics: Understanding Strategic Interaction in Law-making Winter 2020 Policy Evaluation: Methods and Applications Summer 2020 Interest Group Politics Summer 2020 Legislative Politics: Understanding Strategic Interaction in Law-Making Winter 2019 Public Choice Winter 2019 Political Economy Summer 2019 Interest Group Politics Summer 2019 Legislative Politics: Understanding Strategic Interaction in Law-Making Winter 2018 Public Choice Winter 2018 Statistics (Lecture) Summer 2018 Political Institutions: Analysis and Comparison Winter 2017 Legislative Politics: Understanding Strategic Interaction in Law-Making Winter 2017 Interest Group Politics Summer 2017 Experimental Political Science Summer 2017 The Political Economy of the Eurozone Winter 2016 Zeppelin University Friedrichshafen Title Semester Decisions, Games, and Negotiations Spring 2023 Decisions, Games, and Negotiations Spring 2022 Decision and Game Theory Spring 2021 Decision and Game Theory Spring 2020 University of Lucerne Title Semester Experiments in the Social Scieces Fall 2018 London School of Economics and Political Science Module Term GV478 - Political Science and Public Policy Michaelmas 2016 GV225 - Public Choice Lent 2016 GV478 - Political Science and Public Policy Michaelmas 2015 GV478 - Political Science and Public Policy Michaelmas 2014 University of Mannheim Title Semester Methods of Comparative Politics II: Comparative Political Economy Spring 2014 B.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
